Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): Well, I just wonder because we always have the Democrats on and they talk about what Trump's doing. We ask, you know, what are you doing to push back as a Democrat? Obviously, you're the minority. I thought it was interesting. You have a bill that is you're introducing that aims to put guardrails on donations to presidential libraries. I should note that I'm asking you about that as tonight the president is dining
Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): With
Speaker 2: the Qataris at the White House after, of course, they're giving him the plane.
I
Speaker 3: wonder what your expectations are for that. So,
Speaker 4: look, we've had a problem before Donald Trump came along with presidents
Speaker 5 (higher-pitched voice): taking donations to their presidential library while they're still sitting in office and while they can still offer pardons or cut tariff deals or approve mergers. It's just that Donald Trump
has
Speaker 5 (higher-pitched voice): has now just put that on steroids with the $400
Speaker 6: airplane, a $400 million airplane from the Qataris with the settlement
Speaker 5 (higher-pitched voice): of the paramount bogus lawsuit. And who knows?
Speaker 5 (higher-pitched voice): How much other money is being funneled right now into a future
Woman 7: Trump library because there are no rules. There's no rules about having to disclose that money, no caps on disclosing it, and no limits on who can do it. Foreign governments, people seeking pardons, anybody can make these contributions.
Woman 7: So the bill that I introduced, and I've got a group of co-sponsors around this, including Senator Blumenthal here in the Senate. The bill that I've introduced just says, we've got to put some limits on this and say that while you're still president, you can't be out there soliciting or accepting funds
Speaker 8 (higher-pitched voice): from people for your future library. We've got to have just some sensible safeguards in place. And here's what's interesting.
A
Speaker 8 (higher-pitched voice): couple of years ago, the Republicans teamed up with Democrats, with Representative Moskowitz in the House, and they introduced the same bill. We never got it over here, never had a chance
to vote on it. But
Woman 7: this should be a bipartisan effort. It is not in anyone's interest to have a president of the United States even taking on the appearance
of
Woman 7: selling favors to foreign countries or selling favors
Speaker 6: to people who want pardons. And so presidential libraries, let's cut that one off as one of the ways that Donald Trump can wallow in corruption. We'll
Speaker 2: see. I think you might struggle to get some Republican Senate support, but we'll see if that happens.